[{"answer": "His movie career.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 8, "question": "You want me to get drunk and talk to a peacock?", "qSentId": 7}, {"answer": "Alec Baldwin, outspoken, unapologetic, and very, very funny.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "What could be more, what could more of a preposterous waste of our time than that?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, I'm hopeful that he will and I'm -- and that hope is based on the notion that presidents, regardless of party, have more flexibility or perceived flexibility in their second term because there is no possibility for re-election.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Do you think he's actually going to start commissioning those kind of dreamy inspirational projects which will get the whole world gasping and all?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Now the conservative base needs to know that Rick Perry stands with them 110 percent.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "The question is, can you speak for 10 seconds without alienating your base?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "You'd be reading my mind if you said that.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "I mean, when you see, Alec, when you someone like Arnold Schwarzenegger become governor of California, you must think to yourself, I could do at least as good a job as that?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Well, I think that it's something that I used to think about a long, long time ago.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Has part of you always harbored the possibility that you could one day run for the presidency?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Well, I think that the only thing I can day about that is I have some personal favorites, I have people that were nominated that I was excited about and some that I was -- like anybody -- I was maybe perplexed by, if you will.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Who do you fancy?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Well, to the extent that the Oscars, I mean, sometimes those votes as you well know even in recent history, they swing in a very wide track.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "I think they should both -- if they were to win best actress and best actor, to me, that just immediately gives the Oscars that kind of heavyweight glamour, you know?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "You know, she is -- Meryl's -- I'm not going to say anything fresh about her or new that hasn't been said by countless other, you know, more formidable, leading men than I'll ever be.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "What was she like?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "No, of course not.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Was it really Tina Fey's fault, Alec?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "You know, I was very embarrassed and I was very upset because I thought, you know, first of all, that there were people -- I mean, the joke obviously when I got off the plane was there were four other guys Twittering from their cell phones as I was getting kicked off the plane for using my cell phone.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Angry?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "I guess if they gave us -- if they gave us a device on board that we could play Words With Friends while we were flying on the plane with other people on the plane -- play words with friends with other people on board.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Would you ever fly American again?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "We have got the message loud and clear, Alec, although the trouble was hugely entertaining.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "What could be more of a preposterous waste of our time than that?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Oh, I get infinitely more fun from \"30 Rock\" than anything.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Do you get more or less fun from Twitter than you do from \"30 Rock\"?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Well, Yeah, yeah.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "This is the perfect woman for you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "The past is just a blur to me now, Piers.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "I was about to ask you how many times you have been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I just -- my wife gave birth to a little baby girl two months ago.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "You have a child?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Two months ago.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "How long ago?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "She doesn't sleep too badly.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Does she sleep well, your child?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Have I thought about having more kids?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "There's a few of them.", "docId": "120125pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "I have to ask you this, Alec, because I ask everyone this: outside of children and marriage and so on, what has been the single greatest moment of your life, the moment that if I could relive it for you right now, you would ask to relive it?", "qSentId": 537}]